# Murali Krishna M

### Web Developer

As a web developer with 2 years of experience, I have a passion for building intuitive and user-friendly websites and applications. I specialize in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, and have a strong understanding of modern web development frameworks such as Codelgniter 4.



mmuralikrishnammm@gmail.com



Bangalore, India



github.com/M-MuraliKrishna

8904771909

linkedin.com/in/murali-krishna-m

### **EDUCATION**

### **Master's Science in Computer Science REVA University**

09/2020 - 07/2022

Research Paper and Project

Counterfeit Currency Detection App

CGPA: 8.09

## **Bachelor of Computer Application in WebScience**

**Cavalier Animation College** 

07/2016 - 08/2019

CGPA: 5.84

Project

Online Catering Booking System

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **PHP Developer**

Vsnap Technology Solutions

07/2022 - Present Homes247.in its an PropTech Company, Real-Estate based Company

Bangalore,India

- Created Complete HR Panel for attendance and interview candidates track.
- Create Complete Static Website for clients from Homes247.in: www.poorviinfinite.com , www.indiaestates.in
- Tech Stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, PHP, MySQL, CodeIgniter 4.

## Full Stack Web Developer Intern

Star Graphics Business Initiators

10/2021 - 01/2022

Bangalore

### Achievements/Tasks

- Worked on various types of templates and created from scratch.
- To create a full stack web applications and test the sections of built web application.
- Planned, developed, tested, deployed, and maintained web applications. Worked to continually meet the expectations of stakeholders and users.

#### **Software Developer**

Pegasus Equipment Pvt.Ltd

09/2019 - 08/2020

Bangalore

#### Achievements/Tasks

- Designing Front-End forms for client website.
- · Maintaining client website. Supporting for Back-End application like python, Django, and
- Utilized the latest software development tools, techniques and approaches.
- Analyzed and designed new systems and applications. Worked to meet client deadlines.
- Effectively multi tasked and worked well with internal and external teams. Effectively translated client requirements into application designs and system requirements.
- Successfully identified, diagnosed, and fixed website problems, including broken links, typographical errors, and formatting issues.

## SKILLS

WordPress

### PERSONAL PROJECTS

Poorvi Infinite (12/2022 - 02/2023)

https://www.poorviinfinite.com/

India Estates (03/2023 - 05/2023)

http://indiaestates.in/

SS Kuteera (10/2021 - 11/2021)

http://sskuteera.com/

SGK Skills Solutions (01/2022 - 03/2022)

https://sgkskillsolutions.com/

Sri Ram Silks and Sarees (01/2023 - Present)

Working on it

# LANGUAGES

#### Telugu

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency

### English

Professional Working Proficiency

# **INTERESTS AND HOBBIES**

Travelling Fitness Swimming Designing and development websites Researching